Guide to the Washington Area Women's Center records, 1868-1989 MS2344
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Washington Area Women's Center records
1966-1989
1968-1984
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Washington Area Women's Center (Washington, D.C.)
MS2344
30 Linear Feet
During its time from 1972 through the late 1980s, the Washington Area Women's Center served both as a space where women could explore aspects of feminism and work on projects dedicated to furthering feminist theory and also practical work to serve as a clearinghouse of advisors and information to help women in the Metropolitan Area explore all options related to changing their lives and asserting their rights. This collection contains newsletters, correspondence, posters, audio recordings, fliers, programs, meeting minutes, local organization files, reprints, photographs, and handwritten data related to the work performed at the Washington Area Women's Center. The records date from 1868 through 1989 with the bulk of the records falling between 1968-1984.
Scope and Contents note
This collection contains newsletters, correspondence, posters, audio recordings, fliers, programs, meeting minutes, local organization files, reprints, photographs, and handwritten data related to the work performed at the Washington Area Women's Center. The records date from 1868 through 1989 with the bulk of the records falling between 1968-1984.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement
Organized into 9 series: WAWC records, Organizations, Newsletters, Subject files, Reprints, Audiotapes, T-shirts, Graphics, and Unsorted documents.
Biographical / Historical
The Washington Area Women's Center developed naturally from the high level of activism in the Washington area related to feminism and women's rights taking place. Specifically two parallel movements led directly to its formation. First, the Magic Quilt was a coalition of projects and discussion groups. Second, the Women's Liberation Office, an activist group, rented space that it used for meetings, abortion counseling, a telephone hotline, and an information center. The Women's Liberation Office held a retreat at which the idea was born to form a center for women. In 1972, the Washington Area Women's Center formed as a non-profit. Over the years several different management models were attempted including a coordinating council of representatives from different project groups, followed by an elected five-member executive board and finally the group had a core group collective composed of WAWC members who volunteer their time either at the Center or on Center projects. During its time from 1972 through the late 1980s, the Washington Area Women's Center served both as a space where women could explore aspects of feminism and work on projects dedicated to furthering feminist theory and also practical work to serve as a clearinghouse of advisors and information to help women in the Metropolitan Area explore all options related to changing their lives and asserting their rights.
In 1979 the Washington Area Women's Center formed an archives with an understanding that this material would prove extremely useful for the community and protect its history. In 2015 this archives became part of the GW Special Collection Research Center.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Judith Schwarz, 2015 September 9, (2015.049)
Women's rights; Women -- History; Lesbian feminism; Feminist theory; Feminists
- WAWC records, 1972-1989; Series 1
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains correspondence, financial records, meeting minutes, the articles of incorporation for WAWC, and other records related to the organizations work. These records have the date range 1972-1989.
  - Art on the Wall, Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Artlcles of Incorporation, Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Building Search 1978 (old folder), Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Call for Volunteers, Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Community Management Center 1976-1977, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Community Presentation: 1976 Sept 30, 1976 September 30; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Community Presentation: 1977 Feb 15, 1977 February 15; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Coordinating Council Meeting Minutes 1984, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Coordinating Council Meeting Minutes 1985, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Coordinating Council Meeting Minutes 1986, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Coordinating Council Meeting Minutes 1987, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Coordinating Council Meeting Minutes 1988, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Coordinating Council Meeting Minutes 1989, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence pre 1976 and Undated, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence 1976, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence 1977 January to June, 1977 January-June; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence 1977 July to December, 1977 July-December; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence 1978, Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence 1979, Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence 1980, Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Dances, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - DCAFA Liason Minutes 1978, Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board Meetings 1974, Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Extravaganza, Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Federal Tax Info, 1977-1979, Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Financial 1972 Bank Stubs, Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Financial 1973 Journal Sheets, Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Financial 1973-1975 Taxes, Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Financial 1974 Journal Sheets, Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Financial 1974-1975 Annual Budget Proposals and Project Ratings, Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Financial 1975 D.C. Unemployment Compensation Board, Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Financial 1974-1975 Taxes, Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Financial 1975 Canceled checks & Bank Statements, 1974-1975; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Financial 1975 Check Ledger, Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Financial 1975 Journal Sheets, Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Financial 1975 District of Columbia Tax Notes, Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Financial 1975 Feminist Counseling Collective Bills & Receipts, Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Financial 1975 Petty Cash Receipts Jan-May, Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Financial 1975 Petty Cash Receipts July-December, Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Financial 1975 Space Rental Agreements, Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Financial 1977-1978 Invoices, Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Financial 1983, Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Financial 1984, Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Financial 1985, Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Financial 1985 Washington Women's Building Fundraising, Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Financial 1986, Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Financial 1987, Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Financial Fundraising Proposal 1980, Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Financial Flyers 1981, Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Financial Consignment Sales Contract, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Financial Fundraising, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Financial Fundraising Report 1972, Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Fundraising Committee 1972, Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Financial Postal Permit Contracts, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Financial Staff Insurance (offered), Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - History Project, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - History Project Periodicals, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - History Project Stationary, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Internal Business 1976 Sept to December, 1976 September-December; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Internal Business 1977 January to July, 1977 January-July; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Lesbian Heritage/DC, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Lesbian Heritage/DC Correspondence, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Lesbian Heritage/DC Financial, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Lesbian Heritage/DC Indexing Project, Undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Lesbian Heritage/DC Minutes, Undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - WAWC Open House, Undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - "Lesbian Heritage/DC" article by Susanna Sturgis, Undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Mail Log 1976-1977, Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Mail Log 1977-1978, Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Mail Log 1980, Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Mailing List, last labels & photos 1987-1988, Undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Newsletter Ad Policy, Undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Newsletter Annoucements 1977, Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Newsletter Annoucements 1978, Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Newsletter Crossword Puzzle Contest Entries, Jan 1976, Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Newsletter Feedback Sheets, Undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Newsletter Procedure, Undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Newsletter Rough Copy pre 1976, Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Newsletter Rough Copy 1977, Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Newsletter Rough Copy 1978, Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Newsletter Rough Copy 1979, Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Newsletter Volunteers, Undated; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Office Coordinator Books (Contents), Undated; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Picnic, Undated; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Procedures for Desk Staff, Undated; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Professions Day 1977 March 19, Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Program Preliminary Analysis 1974, Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Proposed Washington Womens Resource Center (Employment Project) 1974, Undated; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Publicity 1972, Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Publicity Flyers, Undated; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Questionaires 1982, Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Rap Groups, Undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Rape Speakout 1977 Sept 24, 1977 September 24; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Office and Staff Duties, Undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Physical Locations, Undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Proposals, early 1972, Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Proposals to establish 1972 Aug 15, 1972 August 15; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Proposals Meyer Foundation Grant 1977 May, Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Referrals Housing, Undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Referrals Professional, Undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Security Risk (Virginia) Ginny Ruffalo, Undated; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Sojourner Truth Women's School: Catalogue, Undated; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Sojourner Truth Women's School Fall 1977 Lesbian History Seminar, Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Sojourner Truth Women's School Staff Notes 1981-1982, Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Sport Teams, Undated; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Washington Area Women's Center Photo Diary 1976 [in very bad shape], Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes & Agendas 1976 Oct-Nov, 1976 October-November; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes & Agendas 1976 - 1977, Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes & Agendas 1977 Feb - March, 1977 February-March; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes & Agendas 1977 April - June, Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes & Agendas 1977 July - August, Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes & Agendas 1977 September - October, Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes & Agendas 1977 November - December, Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes & Agendas 1978 January - February, Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes & Agendas 1978 March - April, Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes & Agendas 1978 May - June, Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes & Agendas 1978 July - August, Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes & Agendas 1978 September - October, Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes & Agendas 1979 Jan 7 - Dec 16, 1979 January 7-December 16; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes & Agendas 1980 Jan 13 - July 27, 1980 January 13-July 27; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes & Agendas 1980 August 3 - December 21, Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes & Agendas 1981 January 4 - December 7, Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Staffing Notes, 1981, Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Staffing Schedules 1977 - 1978, Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Structure, Undated; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Student Internship 1979, Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Structure - Past 1975, Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Survey (undated), Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Survey Responses of Feminist Therapists 1978, Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Telephone Log 1975 - 1976, Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Telephone Log 1976 August - December, Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Telephone Log December 1976-January 1977, 1976 December- 1977 January; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Telephone Log 1977 July - December, Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Telephone Log 1977 - 1978, Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Telephone Log 1979, Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Telephone Log 1980, Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Telephone Log 1981 January - May, 1981 January 5-1981 May 28; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Telephone Log 1981 June - December, 1981 June 1-1981 December 31; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Staffing Notes, Undated; Series 1 (Box 11)
  - Women's Nite Out 1978, Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Workshops & Groups, Undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Workshops Contracts, Undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - AACC News, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Affirmations, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Alert, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Alpha Light Center, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - AUS Education Information, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Cassandra, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Center for Women and Religion newsletter (Graduate Theological Union), Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Center for Women's Studies and Services Feminist Bulletin, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - CEW Newsletter, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Choice, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Child Abuse, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - CIM, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Citizen Action in Education, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Colonial Notes: National Lawyer Guild, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Community Women's Center Newsletter, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Community Collective at University of Massachusettes, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Conscience (Catholics for a Free Choice), Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Connections, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - DCAFA, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - D.C. Democratic Economics, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - The D.C. Voter, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - DES National Quarterly, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Do It Now, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Don't Mourn, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Equal Opportunities, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Equal Opportunities Forum, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Equal Times: Capitol Hill NOW, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - E.R.A. Time, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - F.E.W.'s News and Views, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Friendly Women/AFSC Women's Newsletter, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Friends of Ruth, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - The Gibson Report, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Healthright, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - HRW Newsletter, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - In the Running, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - INFACT Update, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - It's Time 1980-1981, Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Marin Women's News Journal, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Maryland Women, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Media Report for Women, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Metropolitan Washington, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - MPOC Women Newsletter (Mass Party Organizing Committee), Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - My Sister's Place News, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - NAGAP Newsletter, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - NARAL News, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - National Association for Girls and Women in Sport/Association for Intercollegiate Athletics for Women News, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - National Association of Women Business Owners, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - National Association Women Business Owners: Capitol, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - NCAN Newsletter: National Coalition of Amrican Nuns, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - NCAWE News, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - National Festival of Women's Theater, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - National Lawyer's Guild, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - National Women's Health Network, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Neighborhood Woman, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - The Network- NJ (New Jersey), Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Nukelessness, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Of a Like Mind, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Pandora, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - People Working Together are Not Helpless, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Potomac Prism, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Preterm, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - PWR Newsletter, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Reproductive Rights Newsletter, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Response, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Sexism in Education, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Spare Rib [1/2], Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Spare Rib [2/2], Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Spirit of '48, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Women and Life on Earth Tidings, 1981; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Valley Women's Voice, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - WEA Women's Studies Newsletter (Great Britain) Education Association, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - WEAL Washington Report, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - WEECN Network News and Notes, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - West Coast Association of Women Historians Newsletter, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - White House News of Women, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Women Against Sexist Violence in Pornography and Media, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Women Against Violence in Pornography and Media Newspage, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Women Against Violence Against Women (WAVAW) Newsletter, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - Women in Action, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - WIA (Women in Action) Newsletter, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - Women in Business and Economic History Newsletter, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - SideBar: Women in Communication, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - Women Against Sexist Violence, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - Women Law Reporter, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - Women New York, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - Women Outdorrs Magazine, 1983; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - Women Today, 1971-1977; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - Women Source, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 88)
  - Womenwise, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 89)
  - Women's Information Bureau, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 90)
  - WIN [Women's International Network] News, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 91)
  - Women's News: Berkshire Capitol District, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 92)
  - Women Writing, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 93)
  - Wree-View, Undated; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 94)
  - Women's Center banner, Series 1 (Box 35, Item 1)
- Organizations, 1968-1984; Series 2
  This series contains fliers, newsletters, brochures and other records for many local, regional, and national organizations related to women's rights. These records have a date range of 1968-1984.
  - Abortion Rights of Washington, D.C., 1979; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    General Note
    Gay Representative's Meeting, Mayor's Conference AND affiliate of National Abortion Rights Action League, 1979
  - Ad Hoc Lesbian Group [formerly "no-name group"], 1979; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Washington, D.C., 6-5-1979
  - Advisory Council on Women's Educational Programs, 1976; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Washington, D.C., 1976
  - Ain't I a Womon? Collective, undated; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Washington, D.C.
  - Amazon Autumn, 1980-1981; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    New Jersey, 1980-81
  - American Association of University Women (AAUW), Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Washington, D.C., 1978
  - American Civil Liberties Union, undated; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    Washington, D.C
  - Artemis Institute, undated; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Baltimore Feminist Network, undated; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    Baltimore, MD
  - Bet Mishpachah Gay Synagogue (originally Metropolitan Community Synagogue), 1979; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    Washington, D.C., 1979
  - Bi-Sexual Group, undated; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    "1968-1978 Past. Present, Future" [history]
  - Black Women's Community Development Foundation, Inc., undated; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    Washington, D.C., 5/31/1905
  - Blue Collar Tradeswomen: Annoucements, undated; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    Washington, D.C.; formerly known as Women in Construction
  - Blue Collar Tradeswomen: Articles of Incorporation, 1979 March 28; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    Washington, D.C., 3-28-1979
  - Blue Collar Tradeswomen: Board of Directors, undated; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Blue Collar Tradeswomen: Bylaws, undated; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Blue Collar Tradeswomen: Correspondence, 1977-1981; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    Washington, D.C., 1977-1981
  - Blue Collar Tradeswomen: Fundraising, undated; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Blue Collar Tradeswomen: Legal Papers, 1975-1977; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    Washington, D.C., 1975-77
  - Blue Collar Tradeswomen: Handbook Originals, undated; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Blue Collar Tradeswomen: Mailing List, undated; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Blue Collar Tradeswomen: Membership, undated; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Blue Collar Tradeswomen: Originals for Printing, undated; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Blue Collar Tradeswomen: Published Articles, undated; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Blue Collar Tradeswomen: Recruitment Info, undated; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Washington, D.C.; newsletters
  - Blue Collar Tradeswomen: The Tradeswoman, undated; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Business & Professional Women's Foundation, undated; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Washington, D.C.; concerts
  - Cantobria Productions, undated; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Charlottesville Lesbian-Feminists, undated; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Charlottesville, VA
  - Chesapeake Area Group of Women Historians, 1980; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Washington, D.C., 1980
  - Coal Employment Project and Coal Mining Women's Support Team, 1980; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Oak Ridge, Tennessee amp;amp;amp; Carbondale, Illinois, 1980
  - Coalition of Gay Sisters (COGS), D.C., 1978; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 11)